Ziady Mubaraq @ziterz

Email: ziterz@icloud.com @ Portfolio @ GitHub @ Twitter @ LinkedIn

SUMMARY

As an experienced and passionate Coding Mentor and Frontend Developer with 5 years of experience, I am proficient in refactoring, debugging, building, teaching, integrating, testing, and developing mobile and website applications at small, medium, and large scales. I also create attractive designs, optimize features, and ensure a smooth user experience.

EXPERIENCE

Learner @ Apple Developer Academy

March 2023 - December 2023

- Learn coding, design, business, and professional skills, such as iOS development, Swift programming, SwiftUI, and HIG principles, in a world-class developer environment provided by Apple.
- Benefit from access to state-of-the-art facilities and a large community of developers.

Lead Instructor of Phase 2 @ Hacktiv8

June 2021 - February 2023

- Collaborate with the Lead Instructor and the team to train and supervise new instructors.
- Evaluate and observe the learning process and instructors by visiting classes and sitting in.
- Ensure that the course material is effectively delivered to students of all abilities and that their needs are met.

Full-Stack JavaScript Instructor @ Hacktiv8

January 2020 - February 2023

- · Teaches, guide and communicate with students.
- · Monitors and assesses students' progress on a regular basis.
- Teaching courses such as Vue.js, Vue Lifecycle, Pinia, React.js, React Hooks, React Native, Redux, Microservices, NoSQL, GraphQL, and Docker.

Frontend Developer @ Imeco

September 2022 - January 2023

- Built an HCIS (Human Capital Information System) application for a company with features such as detailed employee data, company branch data, employee salaries, attendance, and company requirements.
- Using Vue 3, Pinia and TailwindCSS.

Mobile Developer @ Semai

February 2022 - April 2022

- Built an online application called "Speed Online" for ordering tickets for ship crossings in North Kalimantan.
- Using Vue 3, Quasar, Vuex, Geolocation, Payment Gateway, OTP.

Mobile Developer @ Aldeoz Group

October 2020 - December 2020

- Built an application called "JastipinAja" for users who miss their regional food during the pandemic era, providing same-day delivery between cities.
- Using React, React Native, React Hooks, and Paper.

Lead Mobile Developer @ Adira

January 2019 - December 2019

- Built an application called "Dicicilaja" that includes marketplace, sales app, branch office, business rewards, simulation, order in, and inbox features.
- · Using Java Android, Kotlin, Native, Geolocation, Push Notification.

EDUCATION

Computer Science Education, GPA(3.72)

2015 - 2019

Universitas Pendidikan Indonesia, Bandung, Indonesia

Software Engineering

2012 - 2015

Vocational High School 1, Cirebon, Indonesia

Latest version of my resume in available at https://github.com/ziterz/resume